But why not? I'm sixteen.
可是为什么不行? 我都16岁了.
That's right. You just turned sixteen.
对呀. 你才刚刚16岁,
You've just got your driver's license.
才刚刚拿到驾驶执照,
And you are certainly not driving cross-country with a couple of friends for a winter vacation,
当然不可以就和几个朋友驾车横跨美国去过寒假了,
because you don't have enough experience.
因为你还没有足够的经验.
How will I ever get the experience if you never let me do anything?
我怎么可能会有经验呢, 如果你什么事情都不让我去做的话.
I hardly think we are that strict.
我想我们还不至于那么苛刻吧.
But, as you say.
不过,就像你所说的,
you never get to do anything you want.
你永远也不能想做什么就做什么.
It's not fair.
这不公平.
I'm sorry you feel that way.
你这样想我很遗憾.
OK, I won't drive.
那好吧,我不开车,
Just justine and Sarah will.
我让justine和Sarah她们来开.
And they have been driving for months and months.
她们已经开了好多好多个月的车了.
We would be totally careful.
我们会非常小心的.
There's nothing to worry about.
这有什么好担心的.
Why don't you believe me?
为什么你不相信我呢?
It's not that I don't believe you, Beth.
不是我不相信你, Beth.
But the answer is still no.
但我的答复还是不行.
But why?
可是为什么?
You may not take this trip because you are all young,
你不可以参加这次旅行, 因为你们年纪都还太轻,
relatively inexperienced driers.
相对来说又没什么驾驶经验.
Since you're proposing a winter trip,
因为你们提出的是冬季旅行,
this is an even more serious consideration.
那我就更得好好考虑考虑了.
We'd be sick with worry. no matter what you tell us.
不管你对我们怎么说, 我们都会担心死的.
You're just too wonderful to have around the house.
你这么可爱, 家里没你可不行.
You're running for your stupid office.
你在竞选那个愚蠢的官职,
You're doing what you want and we have to accommodate you.
你在做你想做的事,我们非得适应你,
But I can't do what I want.
可我就不能做我想做的事.